Preliminary Inventory of the James Hayes papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- VII. Business transaction contracts (Box 23-44)
  - 1. Sale of farmland (Box 23-38)
    - Tan Li (Folder 27: 16)
    - Wei Xiangquan (Folder 27: 17)
    - Ying Zhen (Folder 27: 18)
    - He Guangrui (Folder 27: 19)
    - He Shenlong (Folder 27: 20)
    - Step mothers of Hu Song Shou, He & Zhang, 1913 (Folder 27: 21)
    - Mo Yunshang,etc. (Folder 27: 22)
    - Sun Shunan (Folder 27: 23)
    - Wu Changyin, etc. (Folder 27: 24)
    - Ya Mei (Folder 27: 25)
    - Zhu Zigang, etc., 1914 (Folder 27: 26)
    - Huang Jietang (Folder 27: 27)
    - Mo Lvzhong (Folder 27: 28)
    - Ouyang Canting, etc. (Folder 27: 29)
    - Ouyang Sun, 1914 (Folder 27: 30)
    - Huang Zhiman Zeng (Folder 28: 1)
    - Liang Xuzhao (Folder 28: 2)
    - Lu Huang (Folder 28: 3)
    - Chen Zhongkui (Folder 28: 4)
    - Wu Deliu, etc. (Folder 28: 5)
    - Zheng Zaiyao (Folder 28: 6)
    - Chen Lixiu, 1913 (Folder 28: 7)
    - Ouyang Wang (Folder 28: 8)
    - Xie Longyao (Folder 28: 9)
    - You He (Folder 28: 10)
    - He Denghan (Folder 28: 11)
    - Jiang jixun (Folder 28: 12)
    - Yang Lizhi, etc. (Folder 28: 13)
    - Huang Wenfa, Huang Jinfa (Folder 28: 14)
    - Lu Cai (Folder 28: 15)
    - Deng Aren (Folder 28: 16)
    - Xu Zhaoyun's wife - Liu (Folder 28: 17)
    - Huang Huanying (Folder 28: 18)
    - Chen Shixian (Folder 28: 19)
    - Li Guangxiu, Li Xiangmao (Folder 28: 20)
    - Li Lida, Mai Lunda (Folder 28: 21)
    - Li XinXiu, etc. (Folder 28: 22)
    - Chen Chixin, 1913 (Folder 29: 1)
    - Deng Gengxin (Folder 29: 2)
    - Hui Cheng,etc. (Folder 29: 3)
    - Pan Yaolai (Folder 29: 4)
    - Zheng Dunming, etc. (Folder 29: 5)
    - Jiang Peixing (Folder 29: 6)
    - Jiang Shaoliang (Folder 29: 7)
    - Jiang Shichang (Folder 29: 8)
    - Jiang Yexiu (Folder 29: 9)
    - Jiang Zhuoxing (Folder 29: 10)
    - Xie Jinguang, etc. (Folder 29: 11)
    - Zhang Houde - Chen (Folder 29: 12)
    - Cai Yanqi, etc. (Folder 29: 13)
    - Cheng Wangzu (Folder 29: 14)
    - He Denghan (Folder 29: 15)
    - Huang Laijiu (Folder 29: 16)
    - Liang Qixuan (Folder 29: 17)
    - Lu Cunyi (Folder 29: 18)
    - Shi Lunchou (Folder 29: 19)
    - Xie Lezhi (Folder 29: 20)
    - Xie - Ye (Folder 29: 21)
    - Xie Shenzhong, Xie Youzhong (Folder 29: 22)
    - Zeng Deyi, Zeng Hanhua (Folder 29: 23)
    - Jiang Shaoliang (Folder 29: 24)
    - Liang Wenhan's wife - He, 1914 (Folder 29: 25)
    - Xie Xiangrui, etc. (Folder 29: 26)
    - Zhou Yayong, 1906 (Folder 29: 27)
    - Cai Pinjie (Folder 30: 1)
    - Cai Raoji (Folder 30: 2)
    - Cai Yanqi, etc. (Folder 30: 3)
    - He Weiguang, etc. (Folder 30: 4)
    - Ou Guangshi, 1913 (Folder 30: 5)
    - Cai Jitai (Folder 30: 6)
    - Cai - Ma (Folder 30: 7)
    - Cheng Jishi (Folder 30: 8)
    - He Guangcheng (Folder 30: 9)
    - Liang Junguang (Folder 30: 10)
    - Pan Zhou (Folder 30: 11)
    - Xie - Zhang (Folder 30: 12)
    - Xie Yongchang, Xie Daihua (Folder 30: 13)
    - Li Jiaju, 1913 (Folder 30: 14)
    - Lin Yongmao (Folder 30: 15)
    - Lu Wenying (Folder 30: 16)
    - Xie Quankai (Folder 30: 17)
    - Xie Yongchang, Xie Daihua (Folder 30: 18)
    - Chen Chengzan, etc. (Folder 30: 19)
    - Jiang Shaoliang's mother - Long (Folder 30: 20)
    - He Huairui (Folder 30: 21)
    - Liang Songfang's wife - Huang (Folder 30: 22)
    - Chen Wen'gao (Folder 31: 1)
    - Xie - Feng (Folder 31: 2)
    - Chen, Chen Tianxi (Folder 31: 3)
    - Li Xing (Folder 31: 4)
    - Dui Xian (Folder 31: 5)
    - Dun Xian, Dun Yuan (Folder 31: 6)
    - Feng Yazhao (Folder 31: 7)
    - Liang Qizhen, etc. (Folder 31: 8)
    - Lu - Zhu Sanpo (Folder 31: 9)
    - Mai Lantai, etc. (Folder 31: 10)
    - Tan Genghe (Folder 31: 11)
    - Yang Huasheng, etc. (Folder 31: 12)
    - Chen Zhantu (Folder 31: 13)
    - Lu - Zhu Sanpo (Folder 31: 14)
    - Feng Jinzhang (Folder 31: 15)
    - He Denghan (Folder 31: 16)
    - Liu Shenxue, etc. (Folder 31: 17)
    - Feng Linxiu, etc. (Folder 32: 1)
    - Huang Yueyun (Folder 32: 2)
    - Liang Junxian's wife (Folder 32: 3)
    - Lin Guangyu, etc. (Folder 32: 4)
    - Lin Shi He Li, etc. (Folder 32: 5)
    - Lu Cunzheng - Kai Lin (Folder 32: 6)
    - Shi Dechun (Folder 32: 7)
    - Zhou Yake, etc. (Folder 32: 8)
    - Cai Benqiao (Folder 32: 9)
    - Chen Yongben, etc. (Folder 32: 10)
    - Liang, Liang Fulin (Folder 32: 11)
    - Yang Yongxiang, etc. (Folder 32: 12)
    - He Guangrui (Folder 32: 13)
    - Liang Hongba, Liang Jiye (Folder 32: 14)
    - Chen Shengsen (Folder 32: 15)
    - Lin Ruixun (Folder 32: 16)
    - Chen Demeng (Folder 33: 1)
    - Chen Renhe Hao (Folder 33: 2)
    - Chang Zhen (Folder 33: 3)
    - He Chaoguang (Folder 33: 4)
    - Lu Chengfu (Folder 33: 5)
    - He Xianchen (Folder 33: 6)
    - Li Bingzhen (Folder 33: 7)
    - Lu Kaili (Folder 33: 8)
    - Lu Mingda (Folder 33: 9)
    - Yuan Guangping (Folder 33: 10)
    - Chen Qianhou, Chen Qianhe (Folder 33: 11)
    - Liang Guitang, etc. (Folder 33: 12)
    - Liang Juheng, etc. (Folder 33: 13)
    - Liang Shaogeng, etc. (Folder 33: 14)
    - Liang Zhongsen (Folder 33: 15)
    - Xiao (Folder 33: 16)
    - Feng Jinzhang (Folder 33: 17)
    - Feng Zhaozhang (Folder 33: 18)
    - He GuanLin, He Yaochen (Folder 33: 19)
    - He Xizhao (Folder 33: 20)
    - Lu yUPIFFang (Folder 33: 21)
    - Su Qitian (Folder 33: 22)
    - Wu Hongzuo (Folder 33: 23)
    - Wu Xunhui, etc., 1918 (Folder 33: 24)
    - Xue Hengfu (Folder 33: 25)
    - Yan Nengyu (Folder 33: 26)
    - Feng Zhaoli (Folder 34: 1)
    - Ouyang Canting (Folder 34: 2)
    - Liang Junxi (Folder 34: 3)
    - Lin Chong'ai, 1923 (Folder 34: 4)
    - Lu Kailian (Folder 34: 5)
    - Longwei Xilin Zhenyou Sao (Folder 34: 6)
    - Ya Jia (Folder 34: 7)
    - He Huailing (Folder 34: 8)
    - He Hualin, etc. (Folder 34: 9)
    - Chen Tanghuan (Folder 34: 10)
    - Chen Zhisun, etc. (Folder 34: 11)
    - Yang Shaojing, etc., 1927 (Folder 34: 12)
    - Chen Yuzhang, etc. (Folder 34: 13)
    - Feng Jinfa (Folder 34: 14)
    - Heshi Dasao (Folder 34: 15)
    - Huang Qingwei (Folder 34: 16)
    - Liu Jiwen, etc. (Folder 34: 17)
    - Feng Wuyuan (Folder 34: 18)
    - He Huailing (Folder 34: 19)
    - Li Jie (Folder 34: 20)
    - Li GanChao (Folder 34: 21)
    - Liao Jingji (Folder 34: 22)
    - Yuan Peiqian (Folder 34: 23)
    - Mu Shun (Folder 35: 1)
    - Xiao Zhenxuan, etc. (Folder 35: 2)
    - Zheng Jinglian, etc. (Folder 35: 3)
    - Chen Jihou, etc., 1938 (Folder 35: 4)
    - Huang Wenjun, etc. (Folder 35: 5)
    - Lin Shaoting, etc. (Folder 35: 6)
    - Liu Jing, He Ru (Folder 35: 7)
    - Xiao Jinshu (Folder 35: 8)
    - Chen Langsheng, 1938 (Folder 35: 9)
    - Chen Weibin (Folder 35: 10)
    - Lin Shaoting (Folder 35: 11)
    - Liu Zhuhong (Folder 35: 12)
    - Yang Zutao (Folder 35: 13)
    - Feng Zuoliang (Folder 35: 14)
    - Mo Lvlian, 1936 (Folder 35: 15)
    - Chen Hongguo, etc. (Folder 35: 16)
    - Chen Youxiang (Folder 35: 17)
    - Feng Jinbiao (Folder 35: 18)
    - Liang Xin, 1937 (Folder 35: 19)
    - Lin Shaoting, 1937 (Folder 35: 20)
    - Luo Shihua (Folder 35: 21)
    - Chen Chongde, 1938 (Folder 36: 1)
    - Chen Dexiang (Folder 36: 2)
    - Chen Rui'en (Folder 36: 3)
    - Chen Xi'en, 1938 (Folder 36: 4)
    - Chen Yongtai, 1938 (Folder 36: 5)
    - Chen Zhaofa, Chen Wenshi, 1939 (Folder 36: 6)
    - Chen Zhengxing, 1938 (Folder 36: 7)
    - Hecheng Company (Folder 36: 8)
    - Xu Taoyao (Folder 36: 9)
    - Yeche Company Ltd. (Folder 36: 10)
    - Zheng Huangshi, etc. (Folder 36: 11)
    - Chen Huanhua, 1940 (Folder 36: 12)
    - Guo Shihai (Folder 36: 13)
    - Lei Xiying (Folder 36: 14)
    - Liang Mulin, 1940 (Folder 36: 15)
    - Liu Shangzhen, 1940 (Folder 36: 16)
    - Luo Rongfu, Luo Rongsheng, 1940 (Folder 36: 17)
    - Luo Shihua, 1940 (Folder 36: 18)
    - Pan Xuquan, 1940 (Folder 36: 19)
    - Pan Yunming, 1940 (Folder 36: 20)
    - Pan Yunsheng, Pan Yunfeng, 1940 (Folder 36: 21)
    - Zhong Huogui, 1940 (Folder 36: 22)
    - Zhong Xiujun (Folder 36: 23)
    - Zhong Yingfu, 1940 (Folder 36: 24)
    - Zhong Yingsong, Zhong Yingjin, 1940 (Folder 36: 25)
    - Chen Caiyou (Folder 36: 26)
    - Jiang Jinfang (Folder 36: 27)
    - Li Xuehai (Folder 36: 28)
    - Liang Juntang (Folder 18: 29)
    - Liang Yaoguang (Folder 36: 30)
    - Ruan Xianxuan (Folder 36: 31)
    - Huang Zizhao, etc. (Folder 37: 1)
    - Li Jixiang (Folder 37: 2)
    - Li Ruxiang (Folder 37: 3)
    - Luo Fupei (Folder 37: 4)
    - Luo Ronghong, etc. (Folder 37: 5)
    - Tang Shifang (Folder 37: 6)
    - Yang Xuehai (Folder 37: 7)
    - Yang Zetang (Folder 37: 8)
    - Ye Zhangda (Folder 37: 9)
    - Zhou Huangshi (Folder 37: 10)
    - Chen Yantang (Folder 37: 11)
    - Huang Zhenhui (Folder 37: 12)
    - Li Yingxiang, 1943 (Folder 37: 13)
    - Lin Guanlian, Ye Bing (Folder 37: 14)
    - Lin Jiao (Folder 37: 15)
    - Lin Ruiting (Folder 37: 16)
    - Liu Enpei (Folder 37: 17)
    - Ruan Chongguang, 1943 (Folder 37: 18)
    - Ruan Kaiming (Folder 37: 19)
    - Ruan Xianxiong (Folder 37: 20)
    - Ruan Xianxuan (Folder 37: 21)
    - Wang Jinfa (Folder 37: 22)
    - Wang Mu'an (Folder 37: 23)
    - Wang Shihua (Folder 37: 24)
    - Yang Xuehai (Folder 37: 25)
    - Zheng Linshi (Folder 37: 26)
    - Zheng Qin (Folder 37: 27)
    - Li Peizhang (Folder 37: 28)
    - Li Shiming (Folder 37: 29)
    - Ruan Xianxuan (Folder 37: 30)
    - Wang An, etc. (Folder 37: 31)
    - Xu Zongwen (Folder 37: 32)
    - Zheng Xiyao (Folder 37: 33)
    - Chen Jixin (Folder 37: 34)
    - Liangtian Xiangyue Sili (Folder 37: 35)
    - Chen Bingshan (Folder 37: 36)
    - Lin Qinyu, etc. (Folder 37: 37)
    - Deng Qianheng (Folder 38: 1)
    - Deng Xiehe (Folder 38: 2)
    - Deng Zhenyuan (Folder 38: 3)
    - Feng Baohuang (Folder 38: 4)
    - Feng Jieliang (Folder 38: 5)
    - Feng Jinpeng, Feng yaosen (Folder 38: 6)
    - Feng Zanxing's wife- Huang (Folder 38: 7)
    - Feng Shida, Feng Shitao (Folder 38: 8)
    - Feng Shitao (Folder 38: 9)
    - Feng Zanxing's wife- Huang (Folder 38: 10)
    - Feng Zuoliang (Folder 38: 11)
    - Li Yaokun, etc. (Folder 38: 12)
    - Lu Niuzai (Folder 38: 13)
    - Zhou Xiling (Folder 38: 14)
    - Zeng Fanpei (Folder 38: 15)
    - Zeng Qingqin (Folder 38: 16)
    - Liang Xiuyue (Folder 38: 17)
    - Yang Bingxin, etc. (Folder 38: 18)
  - 2. Sale of land or pond (Box 39-43)
    - Guan Chufa, 1913 (Folder 39: 1)
    - Guan Yongchang, 1913 (Folder 39: 2)
    - Guan Zhaoxiong, 1913 (Folder 39: 3)
    - Feng Mixian (Folder 39: 4)
    - Liang Yirui (Folder 39: 5)
    - Zhi Bofang (Folder 39: 6)
    - Huang Hongqing, Huang Huaqing (Folder 39: 7)
    - Ying Gui, etc. (Folder 39: 8)
    - He Zhenlin (Folder 39: 9)
    - He Daohong (Folder 39: 10)
    - Luo Maochang (Folder 39: 11)
    - Chen Jiantu (Folder 39: 12)
    - Huang Jianshu, etc. (Folder 39: 13)
    - He Jiancheng, etc. (Folder 39: 14)
    - He Jiancheng, etc. (Folder 39: 15)
    - Huang Yongquan (Folder 39: 16)
    - Wu Yiyun (Folder 39: 17)
    - Chang Wen, Cheng Zu, etc. (Folder 39: 18)
    - Chang Wen, Ying Xiang, etc. (Folder 39: 19)
    - Hong Ze, Chang Wen, etc. (Folder 39: 20)
    - Hong Ze, Ying Xiang, etc. (Folder 39: 21)
    - Ju Cong, etc. (Folder 39: 22)
    - Liang Lianshu (Folder 39: 23)
    - Liang Lianshu (Folder 39: 24)
    - Liang Yingrui, etc. (Folder 39: 25)
    - Zhen Lin, etc. (Folder 39: 26)
    - He Ningbang (Folder 39: 27)
    - Huang Quanqi (Folder 39: 28)
    - Li Shigao (Folder 39: 29)
    - Luo Xianwen (Folder 39: 30)
    - He Hecong (Folder 39: 31)
    - He Huaixiong (Folder 39: 32)
    - Long Yi (Folder 39: 33)
    - Luo Guansheng (Folder 39: 34)
    - Shengping Ju Yixue Shenshi (Folder 40: 1)
    - Lv Jichuan, Li Guangbang (Folder 40: 2)
    - He Chaochang, 1912 (Folder 40: 3)
    - Liang Jieling brothers, 1912 (Folder 40: 4)
    - Tan Yi, Ruan Bafang (Folder 40: 5)
    - Huang Ruzhan (Folder 40: 6)
    - Wang Hengguang, etc. (Folder 40: 7)
    - Huang Shiduan, etc. (Folder 40: 8)
    - Ju Guang (Folder 40: 9)
    - Chen Shaoguang, 1936 (Folder 40: 10)
    - Jiang Chaotai (Folder 40: 11)
    - Shun Zhong (Folder 40: 12)
    - Lu Dongli, etc. (Folder 40: 13)
    - Chao Yuan, He (Folder 40: 14)
    - A Zhi (Folder 40: 15)
    - Tian Zhang brothers (Folder 40: 16)
    - Xie Mingrui, Xie Fangrui (Folder 40: 17)
    - Chen Zhuoxuan, etc. (Folder 40: 18)
    - Liang Tongzu, Liang Shanzu, etc. (Folder 40: 19)
    - Huang Ruilian (Folder 40: 20)
    - Xie Xu (Folder 40: 21)
    - He Jian (Folder 40: 22)
    - Feng Liliang, Feng Jiahu (Folder 40: 23)
    - Fenglian Qinghui (Folder 40: 24)
    - Feng Rongshan (Folder 40: 25)
    - Wang Yayuan (Folder 40: 26)
    - Feng Yuansheng (Folder 40: 27)
    - Pan Zhixiang, etc. (Folder 40: 28)
    - Zheng GuoZu's parents - Weicheng, etc. (Folder 40: 29)
    - Xie - Chen (Folder 41: 1)
    - He Hanfen, etcc. (Folder 41: 2)
    - Huang Ming, Huang Xi (Folder 41: 3)
    - Huang Songnian, Huang Zannian (Folder 41: 4)
    - Ju - Ou (Folder 41: 5)
    - Zhang Peiyuan (Folder 41: 6)
    - Zhang Zuoxiong, etc. (Folder 41: 7)
    - Feng Qiuyuan, Feng Jiangyuan, etc. (Folder 41: 8)
    - Meng Dening (Folder 41: 9)
    - TongDe Tang Zheng Qiao (Folder 41: 10)
    - Fushan Tang (Folder 41: 11)
    - Huang Guokang (Folder 41: 12)
    - Xie Jiaotai (Folder 41: 13)
    - Chen Jianshi (Folder 41: 14)
    - Huang Zizhao (Folder 41: 15)
    - Xie Chunzhong, Xie ? Zhong (Folder 41: 16)
    - Xie Yuanzhi, etc. (Folder 41: 17)
    - Xie Qichang, Xie Dagui, etc. (Folder 41: 18)
    - He Denghan (Folder 41: 19)
    - Huang Lanqing (Folder 41: 20)
    - Huang Zhaoduan, Huang Zhaojun (Folder 41: 21)
    - Xian De, Ya Ao, etc., 1911 (Folder 41: 22)
    - Xie Baocheng, Xie Yongchang, etc. (Folder 41: 23)
    - Huang Yaokai, Huang Yaoguang, etc. (Folder 41: 24)
    - Tongde Tang Yan Zhangmin (Folder 41: 25)
    - Chengde Tang (Folder 42: 1)
    - Huang Ruikang (Folder 42: 2)
    - Lu - Wu (Folder 42: 3)
    - Chen - Shun (Folder 42: 4)
    - Xie Runchang (Folder 42: 5)
    - Wang, Huang Manxiang (Folder 42: 6)
    - Fu Fuqing - Chen (Folder 42: 7)
    - Rui Qian (Folder 42: 8)
    - Mo Chenghui, etc. (Folder 42: 9)
    - Deng Linguang (Folder 42: 10)
    - Huang Xianzhang (Folder 42: 11)
    - Yang Dalun, etc. (Folder 42: 12)
    - Huang Zhaoduan (Folder 42: 13)
    - Wu Hengfu - Wu Qiulian (Folder 42: 14)
    - Huang Yingzhuo (Folder 42: 15)
    - Ya Shuang (Folder 42: 16)
    - Chen Jiucheng - Chen Xiuzong (Folder 42: 17)
    - Li Honggeng (Folder 42: 18)
    - Foshan Bank (Folder 42: 19)
    - Huang Bingwen (Folder 42: 20)
    - Huang Runsong, Huang Runquan (Folder 42: 21)
    - Wu Shan (Folder 42: 22)
    - Xichang Bank(Yin Hao) (Folder 42: 23)
    - Chen Yimian (Folder 43: 1)
    - Kong Jieyuan, Kong Zhongyang (Folder 43: 2)
    - Li Chengjiu - Yushu (Folder 43: 3)
    - Chen Fuqing - Weikui (Folder 43: 4)
    - Liang Yunqing, Liang Zhaoshi (Folder 43: 5)
    - Chen Fuqing (Folder 43: 6)
    - Nanyue Company (Folder 43: 7)
    - Lin Ansheng (Folder 43: 8)
    - Tan Lianggui (Folder 43: 9)
    - Liu Huimao (Folder 43: 10)
    - Xie Mengxing (Folder 43: 11)
    - Ganji Cheng (Folder 43: 12)
    - Hede Tang, He Fengchu, etc. (Folder 43: 13)
    - Mei Qiao compnay (Folder 43: 14)
    - Liu Xinsheng (Folder 43: 15)
    - Liu Xinsheng (Folder 43: 16)
    - Xu Chengtagn (Folder 43: 17)
    - Fu - Li Yayi (Folder 43: 18)
    - Wu Minfen (Folder 43: 19)
    - Cheng Changxi (Folder 43: 20)
    - Chen Tianxi, Chen Zhitang (Folder 43: 21)
    - Chen zhaonuo, etc. (Folder 43: 22)
    - Yang Ruixian, etc. (Folder 43: 23)
    - Wang Shengsan (Folder 43: 24)
    - Mai Yongde - Ruan Song (Folder 43: 25)
    - Xu Chengtang (Folder 43: 26)
    - Yu Hailun (Folder 43: 27)
    - Liang Zhoushi (Folder 43: 28)
    - Feng Di (Folder 43: 29)
  - 3. Sale of house (Box 44-46)
    - Chen Tinghui (Folder 44: 1)
    - Meng You'en (Folder 44: 2)
    - Liang Jianzhong's wife - Zhang (Folder 44: 3)
    - Li Weigui (Folder 44: 4)
    - Mii Mingxian (Folder 44: 5)
    - Liang Huaizu, Liang xingzu (Folder 44: 6)
    - Xie En (Folder 44: 7)
    - Cai Liangshi (Folder 44: 8)
    - Wu Chenglai (Folder 44: 9)
    - Lu Gong'an (Folder 44: 10)
    - Shengping Ju Shenshi (Folder 44: 11)
    - Yang Liangzhi, Yang Quanzhi (Folder 44: 12)
    - Liu Runfu, Liu Runhua (Folder 44: 13)
    - Jiang Congkuan (Folder 44: 14)
    - Jiangmen - Lao (Folder 44: 15)
    - Lian'an Huaitang (Folder 44: 16)
    - Chen Zhaojian (Folder 44: 17)
    - Jiang Yakuan, Jiang's mother Lao (Folder 44: 18)
    - Gou Fangkun (Folder 44: 19)
    - Liang Xianda, Liang Shizhen (Folder 44: 20)
    - Zhang Qudande (Folder 44: 21)
    - Pan Xincheng (Folder 44: 22)
    - Chen Yuanji (Folder 44: 23)
    - Huang Jin'an (Folder 44: 24)
    - Liang Zhongshan (Folder 44: 25)
    - Su He (Folder 44: 26)
    - He Hongjin (Folder 44: 27)
    - Xie Yuhua, Xie Jianhua (Folder 44: 28)
    - Peng Guangfu (Folder 44: 29)
    - Hu Jishan (Folder 45: 1)
    - Chen Xiangui (Folder 45: 2)
    - Dong Kunshi, 1913 (Folder 45: 3)
    - He Yutong (Folder 45: 4)
    - He Yunheng (Folder 45: 5)
    - Wu ? (Folder 45: 6)
    - Yang Jisi -Yang Naitang (Folder 45: 7)
    - Cao Chengde (Folder 45: 8)
    - Li Zeli, 1913 (Folder 45: 9)
    - Lifan Yu Tang (Folder 45: 10)
    - Chueng ye tuan (Folder 45: 11)
    - Li Baichuan (Folder 45: 12)
    - Zhan Xuejin (Folder 45: 13)
    - Cui Shaonan (Folder 45: 14)
    - Tongde Gao Jinguang, etc. (Folder 45: 15)
    - Huang Yong'an (Folder 45: 16)
    - Lu Yanxiang (Folder 46: 1)
    - Yang Zhipen (Folder 46: 2)
    - Lu Runfang (Folder 46: 3)
    - Jiao Tai (Folder 46: 4)
    - Ming Hu (Folder 46: 5)
    - Jiangmeng - Long (Folder 46: 6)
    - Huang Shuntang, 1924 (Folder 46: 7)
    - Zheng Wenming, 1938 (Folder 46: 8)
    - Huang Zhaoduan (Folder 46: 9)
    - Huang Guozheng (Folder 46: 10)
    - Yu Deheng (Folder 46: 11)
    - Shu Zai (Folder 46: 12)
    - Cai - Lin (Folder 46: 13)
    - Lian, Lian Zhaozong, grandson: Lian Feng (Folder 46: 14)
    - TongHongyu Tang, Tong sheng (Folder 46: 15)
    - Yurong - Yu Ande (Folder 46: 16)
    - Chengyuan Tang - Tan Dianru (Folder 46: 17)
    - Jiang Liang (Folder 46: 18)
    - Tan Wennuan (Folder 46: 19)
    - Zeng Lianrun (Folder 46: 20)
    - Tan Wenshi, 1938 (Folder 46: 21)
    - Guan Chan (Folder 46: 22)
    - Huang Zhaoming, etc. (Folder 46: 23)
    - Liu Shiyou (Folder 46: 24)
    - Chen Yongnong (Folder 46: 25)
    - Liu Jialian, Liu Renzheng (Folder 46: 26)
    - Wan'an Tang - Mai Guanghuan (Folder 46: 27)
    - Feng Jinkai, mother - Mo (Folder 46: 28)
    - Feng Yongliang, Feng Baoliang (Folder 46: 29)
  - 4. Sale of shop (Box 47-48)
    - Chen Zhangyuan (Folder 47: 1)
    - Zheng Haorong (Folder 47: 2)
    - Zeng Pinchang (Folder 47: 3)
    - Guan Yuanda, Guan Huada (Folder 47: 4)
    - Qiu Lean Tang (Folder 47: 5)
    - Liang Zhaorong, 1918 (Folder 47: 6)
    - Pan Xiqi (Folder 47: 7)
    - Wu Jihou (Folder 47: 8)
    - He Shunhe (Folder 47: 9)
    - Zhang Fuqian (Folder 47: 10)
    - Luo Houde, Liu lan (Folder 47: 11)
    - Yang Bingsong, etc. (Folder 47: 12)
    - Mai Liangshi (Folder 47: 13)
    - Zhang Xianghe (Folder 47: 14)
    - Yu Yuehui, Yu Yinglin (Folder 47: 15)
    - Fuyin Tang (Folder 47: 16)
    - Zhang Yinmo, etc. (Folder 47: 17)
    - Li Quanfu (Folder 47: 18)
    - Ding Zhixiang (Folder 47: 19)
    - Liang Minchu (Folder 47: 20)
    - Lin Ruqin (Folder 47: 21)
    - Yang Jisi (Folder 47: 22)
    - Chong Litang - Li Fu, Li You (Folder 47: 23)
    - Gonghe Tang (Folder 47: 24)
    - Jingye Tang (Folder 48: 1)
    - Jingye Tang (Folder 48: 2)
    - Jingye Tang (Folder 48: 3)
    - Jingye Tang (Folder 48: 4)
    - Ye Shuji Tang Mingde, 1913 (Folder 48: 5)
    - Chen Chaoxun (Folder 48: 6)
    - Chen Shude, 1929 (Folder 48: 7)
    - Chen Binheng (Folder 48: 8)
    - Liang Fali - Liang Huan (Folder 48: 9)
    - Hehe Tang, 1921 (Folder 48: 10)
    - Jiang Huisen (Folder 48: 11)
    - Huang Yuqing - Huang Shaojie (Folder 30: 12)
    - Chen Hanyang (Folder 48: 13)
    - Jiang Er Bang (Folder 48: 14)
    - Hecheng Tang - Chen Hede, Wu Chengye (Folder 48: 15)
    - Sanyun Tang - Long Ronghai, 1930 (Folder 48: 16)
    - Jiang Zhuo (Folder 48: 17)
    - Shi Jiaxuan (Folder 48: 18)
    - Feng Yao (Folder 48: 19)
    - Huang Zuozhao (Folder 48: 20)
    - Yude Tang - Shi Jiaxuan, Yu Jihe (Folder 48: 21)
    - Zhou Yongsong - Zhou Xueqiao (Folder 48: 22)
    - Chen-Zeng (Folder 48: 23)
    - Chen Youxiang (Folder 48: 24)
    - Feng Bingjun (Folder 48: 25)
    - Feng Shaohe (Folder 48: 26)
    - Rongye tang Huang Shirong (Folder 48: 27)
  - 5. Sale of orchard or grain farm (Box 49)
    - Zhen Xian (Folder 49: 1)
    - Jin Jibo (Folder 49: 2)
    - Gao Kunyuan (Folder 49: 3)
    - He Diahuang (Folder 49: 4)
    - Zhengmen - Hu, Zhengjuelan (Folder 49: 5)
    - Zhou Yamu (Folder 49: 6)
    - Zhou Yazhuan (Folder 49: 7)
    - Jia Gu (Folder 49: 8)
    - JiaShu Qianhe (Folder 49: 9)
    - JiaShu Qianhe (Folder 49: 10)
    - Zhen Qun (Folder 49: 11)
    - Chen Yanheng (Folder 49: 12)
    - Lin Benshi, Lin-Chen Miss (Folder 49: 13)
    - Yu Jinzhang (Folder 49: 14)
    - Zong Shu Deli (Folder 49: 15)
    - Chen (Folder 49: 16)
    - Liu Qianxing, etc. (Folder 49: 17)
    - Liu Lunkai..etc (Folder 49: 18)
    - Liu Xigen (Folder 49: 19)
    - Liu Zhongshi, Liu Shusen (Folder 49: 20)
  - 6. Sale of toilet (Box 49)
    - Zuo Dong (Folder 49: 21)
    - Chen zhishou, Chen Zhushou (Folder 49: 22)
- VIII. Forfeiture, exchange, or transfer of ownership contracts (Box 50-53)
  - 1. Forfeiture of land ownership (Box 50-51)
    - Zhou Shuzhao (Folder 50: 1)
    - Huang Binyu, Huang Qing,yue) (Folder 50: 2)
    - Luo Zhangqi (Folder 50: 3)
    - Xin Luan (Folder 50: 4)
    - Lv Yuxiu (Folder 50: 5)
    - Shicheng Zhong tang (Folder 50: 6)
    - Shicheng Zhong tang (Folder 50: 7)
    - Shi Qingshi (Folder 50: 8)
    - Rong Zhichen (Folder 50: 9)
    - Zhong Tao, etc.s (Folder 50: 10)
    - Liang, Shaoting (Folder 50: 11)
    - Zhang, Qiying (Folder 50: 12)
    - Yanjiu (Folder 50: 13)
    - Wang Hengmao, etc. (Folder 50: 14)
    - Chen Yaqian, Chen Zhongwo' (Folder 50: 15)
    - Peng Ruicheng, 1932 (Folder 50: 16)
    - Jiangshi, 1932 (Folder 50: 17)
    - Jiang You (Folder 50: 18)
    - Li Yongzhen, Li Shunguang (Folder 50: 19)
    - Liang He (Folder 50: 20)
    - Chi Fu (Folder 50: 21)
    - Jiang Jingde (Folder 50: 22)
    - Li Juren (Folder 50: 23)
    - Tan Hongshu (Folder 50: 24)
    - Yang Rong (Folder 50: 25)
    - Li Yunbo (Folder 50: 26)
    - Fan Jiazhi, etc. (Folder 50: 27)
    - Su Peng (Su Shuquan), 1932 (Folder 51: 1)
    - Yan Zirong, 1932 (Folder 51: 2)
    - Ye Yi, Ye Ying, 1932 (Folder 51: 3)
    - Chen Dongquan (Folder 51: 4)
    - Li Yankai (Folder 51: 5)
    - Li Yanyi (Folder 51: 6)
    - Huang Funing (Folder 51: 7)
    - Huang Songjia (Folder 51: 8)
    - Li Yi (Folder 51: 9)
    - Xie Ankang, Xi Ming (Folder 51: 10)
    - Feng Quanling (Folder 51: 11)
    - Liang Yuji (Folder 51: 12)
    - Zhuo Feng, Zhuo Lu, 1937 (Folder 51: 13)
  - 2. Exchange of land, Zhou Yashen (Folder 52: 1)
  - 3. Exchange of vegetable plot, Tongxiang Di Ya Si (Folder 52: 2)
  - 4. Transfer of house ownership, Pan Hui, Pan Hu (Folder 52: 3)
  - 5. Transfer of land ownership, Lu Kaidi (Folder 52: 4)
  - 6. Transfer of shop ownership, Feng Jinghu, Feng Jingyang (Folder 52: 5)
  - 7. Split-up deed (Box 52)
    - Chunsheng, Shangcheng (Folder 52: 6)
    - Dongyue Company - Wang Ziming (Folder 52: 7)
    - Hecheng (Folder 52: 8)
    - Mei Qiao Company - Liangmin (Folder 52: 9)
    - Liu Jinxing - Liu Chuiyuan, Liu Renzheng, No. 1179 (Folder 52: 10)
    - Liu Jinxing - Liu Chuiyuan, Liu Renzheng, No. 1180 (Folder 52: 11)
- IX. Lease contract (Box 52)
  Arranged in groups by type of lease, then by owner
  - 1. Lease of farmland (Box 52)
    - Liao Dianzhao (Folder 52: 12)
    - Liao Dianzhao (Folder 52: 13)
  - 2. Lease of land (Box 52)